[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mercury was named after the Roman Messenger of the gods. What is the name of the corresponding god in Greek mythology?", "correct_answer": "Hermes", "incorrect_answers": ["Zeus", "Hera", "Apollo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is it true that in the movie Next Friday, Craig flees to live with Uncle Elroy because Deebo breaks out of prison?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the period that the 1975 comedy movie Shampoo spans?", "correct_answer": "24 hours", "incorrect_answers": ["A month", "A week", "1 hour"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not within the natural diet of the omnivorous Eastern Box Turtle?", "correct_answer": "Small amphibians", "incorrect_answers": ["Earthworms", "Snails", "Carrion"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why are foods basted?", "correct_answer": "To prevent them from drying out", "incorrect_answers": ["To give them a crunchy crust", "To add flavor", "To give them a brown surface"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following characters is a chicken?", "correct_answer": "Foghorn Leghorn", "incorrect_answers": ["Dori", "Daffy", "Kermit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Mannheim, Germany, people began recycling this.", "correct_answer": "Dead pets to make fertilizer", "incorrect_answers": ["Coffee grinds to make jewelry", "Old PCs to make radar equipment  for traffic control", "Old swords and knives to make I-beams"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Europe goldfish were first introduced to what country?", "correct_answer": "Portugal", "incorrect_answers": ["France", "England", "Italy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of underwear does Pinocchio from the Shrek movies accidentally reveal he wears?", "correct_answer": "Thongs", "incorrect_answers": ["Tidy whities", "Lacy briefs", "Pink girlie panties"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Anglo-Saxon times the bride stood on the left of the groom to allow him to keep his right sword hand free so that he could fight off anyone trying to kidnap the bride.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do these people have in  common: Star Jones, Randy Jackson, President Dwight David Eisenhower, Carnie Wilson, Diego Maradona?", "correct_answer": "They have all had gastric bypass surgery.", "incorrect_answers": ["They have all appeared on the long running BBC show Leaders of Our Times.", "They have all been cited by the UN for their work with  UNICEF.", "They have all received  he Legiondaire Grand Award."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this movie Alvy comes to his ex-girlfriend\u2019s rescue and heroically battles the spider in her bathroom with a tennis racquet.", "correct_answer": "Annie Hall", "incorrect_answers": ["All That Jazz", "The Goodbye Girl", "Heaven Can Wait"]}]